Love will lead you home
How I Live Now is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Kevin Macdonald.
An American girl, sent to the English countryside to stay with relatives, finds love and
purpose while fighting for her survival as war envelops the world around her.
Daisy Ryback, played by Saoirse Ronan.
Eddie, played by George MacKay.
Isaac, played by Tom Holland.
Piper, played by Harley Bird.
Joe, played by Danny McEvoy.
Aunt Penn, played by Anna Chancellor.
How I Live Now is a 2013 romantic speculative drama film based on
the 2004 novel of the same name by Meg Rosoff.
It was directed by Kevin Macdonald, written by Tony Grisoni, Jeremy Brock and Penelope Skinner while starring
Saoirse Ronan, George MacKay, Tom Holland, Harley Bird, Anna Chancellor and  Corey Johnson.
The film centres around American teenager, Daisy (Ronan) and her British cousins, Eddie (MacKay), Isaac
(Holland), and Piper (Bird), as they try to reunite during an apocalyptic nuclear war.
The film premiered at the 2013 Toronto International Film Festival and received mixed reviews, with some critics
positively comparing Ronan's role to Jennifer Lawrence's role as Katniss Everdeen in The Hunger Games.
The film was nominated for multiple awards across various categories including Ronan
being nominated for a British Independent Film Award and a Saturn Award.
Macdonald, MacKay and Bird also received various nominations.
The film explores themes of countryside, based on novel or book,
post-apocalyptic future, survival, terrorism.
The tone is emotional and intense.